Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  - Champions
    - The Olympians. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1990., D04563884 (Box BG 39, Volume 2270)
    - Champions Presents. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1991., D04564010K (Box BG 39, Volume 2267)
    - Classic Organizations (#416). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1991., D04563923W (Box BG 39, Volume 2172)
    - European Enemies. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1991., D04564011L (Box BG 39, Volume 2268)
    - Road Kill. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1991., D04563883. (Box BG 39, Volume 2269)
    - Champions of the North. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1992., D04564004N (Box BG 39, Volume 2261)
    - Champions Universe (#421). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1992., D04563833W (Box BG 39, Volume 2150)
    - High Tech Enemies. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1992., D04564003M (Box BG 39, Volume 2260)
    - Normals Unbound (#420). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1992., D04563834X (Box BG 39, Volume 2151)
    - Allies. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D045639992 (Box BG 39, Volume 2256)
    - Champions Presents #2. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04564002L (Box BG 39, Volume 2259)
    - Dark Champions: Heroes of Vengeance. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04563995+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2252)
    - The Mutant File. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D045639981 (Box BG 39, Volume 2255)
    - Viper. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04564001K (Box BG 39, Volume 2258)
    - Golden Age Champions (#436). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563918- (Box BG 39, Volume 2167)
    - Pyramid in the Sky (#437). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563917Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2166)
    - Atlantis (#441). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1995., D04563843X (Box BG 39, Volume 2162)
    - Enemies Assemble! (#440). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1995., D04563844Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2163)
    - Enemies for Hire (#439). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1995., D04563845Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2164)
    - Watchers of the Dragon (#442). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1995., D04563842W (Box BG 39, Volume 2161)
    - Blood Fury. Published by Roseville, MN: Atlas Games, 1996., D04563840U (Box BG 39, Volume 2157)
    - Foxbat Unhinged. Published by Roseville, MN: Atlas Games, 1996., D04563873- (Box BG 39, Volume 2158)
    - Heroic Adventures, Volume 1. Published by Elk Grove, CA: Gold Rush Games, 1996., D04563839 (Box BG 39, Volume 2156)
    - Atlas Unleashed (#48). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, date unknown., D04563813U (Box BG 39, Volume 2101)
    - GM Screen and Accessories for Champions. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises,., D04563893 (Box BG 39, Volume 2283)
  - Champions: New Millennium
    - Alliances. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1997., D04563835Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2152)
    - Bay City. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1997., D04563837- (Box BG 39, Volume 2154)
    - Champions: New Millennium. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1997., D04563836Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2153)
  - Children of Prophecy
    - Tribe 8. Published by Montreal, QC: Dream Pod 9, Inc., 1998., D03574342S (Box BG 39, Volume 618)
    - Tribe 8: Weaver's Screen and Assistant. Published by Montreal, QC: Dream Pod 9, Inc., 1998., D04382285W (Box BG 39, Volume 619)
    - Vimary. Published by Montreal, QC: Dream Pod 9, Inc., 1998., D03574329X (Box BG 39, Volume 670)
    - Children of Lilith. Published by Montreal, QC: Dream Pod 9, Inc., 1999., D03574330P (Box BG 39, Volume 669)
    - Tribe 8: Companion. Published by Montreal, QC: Dream Pod 9, Inc., 1999., D03574331Q (Box BG 39, Volume 668)
  - Chill
    - Highland Terror. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1984., D04382865- (Box BG 39, Volume 1162)
    - Vengeance of Dracula. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1984., D04382866. (Box BG 39, Volume 1163)
    - Village of Twilight. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1984., D04382864Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1161)
    - Haunter of the Moor. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1985., D04382867 (Box BG 39, Volume 1164)
    - Thutmose's Night. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1985., D04382869/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1165)
  - Chivalry and Sorcery
    - Vampires. Published by Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd., 1985., D04382763X (Box BG 39, Volume 1132)
    - Chivalry and Sorcery: Warfare and Wizardry in the Feudal Age. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1977., D04403619R (Box BG 39, Volume 1438)
    - Bireme and Galley: Naval Warfare, Egypt to Lepanto. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04403794V (Box BG 39, Volume 1584)
    - Destrier. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04383074T (Box BG 39, Volume 1443)
    - Sourcebook. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04403616O (Box BG 39, Volume 1441)
    - Swords and Sorcerers. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1978., D04403618Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1439)
    - Saurians. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1979., D04403617P (Box BG 39, Volume 1440)
    - Sourcebook 2. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1981., D04383075U (Box BG 39, Volume 1442)
    - Chivalry and Sorcery, 3rd edition. Published by Sound Beach, NY: Highlander Designgs, 1996., D04403622L (Box BG 39, Volume 1446)
  - Conan
    - Conan: The Roleplaying Game. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2003., D04564059X (Box BG 39, Volume 2320)
    - Game Master's Screen. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2003., D04563901S (Box BG 39, Volume 2314)
    - Pocket Edition. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2003., D04564030M (Box BG 39, Volume 2300)
    - Across the Thunder River. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2004., D04564055T (Box BG 39, Volume 2316)
    - Pirate Isles. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2004., D04564056U (Box BG 39, Volume 2317)
    - The Free Companies. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2004., D04564054S (Box BG 39, Volume 2315)
    - The Road of Kings. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2004., D04564057V (Box BG 39, Volume 2318)
    - The Scrolls of Skelos. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2004., D04564058W (Box BG 39, Volume 2319)
    - Aquilonia - Flower of the West. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04564053R (Box BG 39, Volume 2313)
    - Conan and the Heretics of Tarantia. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04563900R (Box BG 39, Volume 2309)
    - Conan and the Lurking Tower of Nahab. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D045638991 (Box BG 39, Volume 2307)
    - Conan and the Tower of the Elephant. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D045638980 (Box BG 39, Volume 2306)
    - Hyboria's Fallen: Pirates, Thieves and Temptresses. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04564035R (Box BG 39, Volume 2308)
    - Hyboria's Fiercest: Barbarians, Borders and Nomads. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04564052Q (Box BG 39, Volume 2312)
    - Hyboria's Finest: Nobles, Scholars and Soldiers. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04564036S (Box BG 39, Volume 2310)
    - Tales of the Black Kingdoms. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2005., D04564037T (Box BG 39, Volume 2311)
    - Conan and the Reavers of the Vilayet. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2006., D04563897% (Box BG 39, Volume 2301)
    - Faith and Fervour. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2006., D04564032O (Box BG 39, Volume 2303)
    - Ruins of Hyboria. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2006., D04564031N (Box BG 39, Volume 2302)
    - Stygia - Serpent of the South. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2006., D04564034Q (Box BG 39, Volume 2305)
    - Tito's Trading Post. Published by Mongoose Publishing Ltd., 2006., D04564033P (Box BG 39, Volume 2304)
    - Royal Armies of the Hyborean Age. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1975., D04403876W (Box BG 39, Volume 1698)
  - Coriolis
    - Burning Shaolin. Published by Roseville, MN: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382209S (Box BG 39, Volume 477)
    - Burning Shaolin. Published by Roseville, MN: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382208R (Box BG 39, Volume 478)
  - Creature Crucible
    - Tall Tales of the Wee Folk. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382480T (Box BG 39, Volume 853)
    - Top Ballista. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382481U (Box BG 39, Volume 854)
    - The Sea People. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382482V (Box BG 39, Volume 855)
    - Night Howlers. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382483W (Box BG 39, Volume 856)
  - Crimson Skies
    - Behind the Crimson Veil (#8003). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563984$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2240)
    - Wings over Manhattan (#8002). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1999., D04563882- (Box BG 39, Volume 2241)
    - Aircraft Manual (#8004). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563881Z (Box BG 39, Volume 2239)
    - Blake Aviation Security (#8006). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563880Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2238)
    - Pride of the Republic (#8007). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563983 (Box BG 39, Volume 2237)
    - The Airman's Gazetteer (#8008). Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 2000., D04563982. (Box BG 39, Volume 2236)
  - Cyber Generation
    - Bastille: Keep on Rockin' for a Free World. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04403645Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1286)
    - Eco Front: Reachin' Out for the Eden Dream: A Documents of the Revolution Sourcebook. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04382745X (Box BG 39, Volume 1285)
    - Evolve or Die. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04382669 (Box BG 39, Volume 1393)
    - Media Front: A Documents of the Revolution Sourcebook. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04382746Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1284)
    - Evolve or Die: Revolution 2, 2nd edition. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382742U (Box BG 39, Volume 1288)
    - Virtual Front: Because Reality is Obsolete: A Documents of the Revolution Sourcebook. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382741T (Box BG 39, Volume 1289)
  - Cyberpunk
    - Deep Space: Take Cyberpunk to the Final Frontier. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1989., D03806291T (Box BG 39, Volume 273)
    - Hardwired: The Sourcebook. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1989., D03804414O (Box BG 39, Volume 291)
    - Journal of the Corporate Mercenary Solo of Fortune. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1989., D03804413N (Box BG 39, Volume 292)
    - Near Orbit: Space Supplement for Cyberpunk. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1989., D03804415P (Box BG 39, Volume 290)
    - Rockerboy. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1989., D03804416Q (Box BG 39, Volume 289)
    - Chrome Book. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804419T (Box BG 39, Volume 284)
    - Corporate Report 2020. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804421M (Box BG 39, Volume 282)
    - Cyberpunk: The Roleplaying Game of the Dark Future, 2nd edition. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804412M (Box BG 39, Volume 293)
    - Euro Source: The Eurotheatre Sourcebook for Cyberpunk. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804420L (Box BG 39, Volume 283)
    - Night City. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804417R (Box BG 39, Volume 288)
    - Tales from the Forlorn Hope: Eight Adventures for Cyberpunk. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1991., D03804422N (Box BG 39, Volume 281)
    - The Arasaka Brainworm. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1991., D04403697X (Box BG 39, Volume 1532)
    - All Fall Down. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1992., D04403695V (Box BG 39, Volume 1528)
    - Chasing the Dragon. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1992., D04403710J (Box BG 39, Volume 1529)
    - Chrome Book 2: The Cyberpunk Style Guide Vol. 2. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D03806286X (Box BG 39, Volume 277)
    - Corporation Report 2020 Vol. 2. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D03017050G (Box BG 39, Volume 280)
    - Corporation Report 2020 Vol. 3. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D03806284V (Box BG 39, Volume 279)
    - Necrology of Life, Death and Afterwards. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1992., D04383078X (Box BG 39, Volume 1433)
    - Night's Edge. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1992., D04383081R (Box BG 39, Volume 1432)
    - Protect and Serve. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D03806285W (Box BG 39, Volume 278)
    - The Chrome Berets. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1992., D04403708Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1527)
    - The Crisis Chip. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1992., D04403696W (Box BG 39, Volume 1530)
    - When Gravity Fails: Adventuring in the World of George Alec Effinger's Novels. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1992., D03804418S (Box BG 39, Volume 285)
    - Cyberpunk 2.0.2.0. Character Sheets. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D04382125P (Box BG 39, Volume 287)
    - Eurotour: Danger and Death on a Euro-Rock Tour. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D03806288Z (Box BG 39, Volume 276)
    - Guide to the Net: The Cyberpunk Sourcebook for the Global Computer Net. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D03806292U (Box BG 39, Volume 272)
    - Home of the Brave: The Sourcebook for America in the Dark Future. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D03806290S (Box BG 39, Volume 274)
    - King of the Concrete Jungle. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1993., D04383079Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1436)
    - Maximum Metal: High-Powered Ordinace for Cyberpunk 2020. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D03806289- (Box BG 39, Volume 275)
    - Necrology and Now I Lay Me Down. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1993., D04383076V (Box BG 39, Volume 1434)
    - Necrology: Immortality…. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1993., D04383080Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1435)
    - Survival of the Fittest. Published by Montreal, Qc., Canada: Ianus Publications, Inc., 1993., D04383077W (Box BG 39, Volume 1437)
    - Thicker than Blood. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1993., D04403694U (Box BG 39, Volume 1526)
    - Wild Side: The Cyberpunk Sourcebook for the Street. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1993., D03806294W (Box BG 39, Volume 271)
    - Chrome 3 Book: The Cyberpunk Style Guide Vol. 3. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1994., D03806297Z (Box BG 39, Volume 259)
    - Journal of the Corporate Mercenary Solo of Fortune 2. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1994., D03804349V (Box BG 39, Volume 258)
    - Listen Up, You Primative Screwheads!!!: The Unexpurgated Cyberpunk Referee's Guide. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1994., D03806293V (Box BG 39, Volume 270)
    - Pacific Rim Sourcebook. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1994., D03806299. (Box BG 39, Volume 268)
    - Rough Guide to the U.K.: Riding the Edge to 2020's Britain. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1994., D03806298- (Box BG 39, Volume 269)
    - Blackhand's Street Weapons 2020, 1st edition. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D04382123N (Box BG 39, Volume 264)
    - Edgerunners Inc.: The Cyberpunk Classifieds for 2020. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D03806283U (Box BG 39, Volume 266)
    - Eurosource Plus: The New Eurotheater Sourcebook for Cyberpunk. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D03806281S (Box BG 39, Volume 265)
    - Neo Tribes: The Nomads of North America. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1995., D03806300K (Box BG 39, Volume 267)
    - Brainware Blowout: The Hardware and Software Compendium for Cyberpunk. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1996., D03806296Y (Box BG 39, Volume 260)
    - Chrome Book: The Cyberpunk Syle Guide Vol. 4. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1996., D03804340M (Box BG 39, Volume 257)
    - Live and Direct: Multimedia in the Cyberpunk Age. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1996., D03806295X (Box BG 39, Volume 261)
    - Firestorm: Shockwave The Fourth Corporate War Book Two. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1997., D03806287Y (Box BG 39, Volume 262)
    - Firestorm: Stormfront The Fourth Corporate War Book One. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, 1997., D03806282T (Box BG 39, Volume 263)
    - Cyberpunk: The Roleplaying Game of the Dark Future Data Screen. Published by Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games, undated., D04382124O (Box BG 39, Volume 286)
    - Night City Stories. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1992., D04403711K (Box BG 39, Volume 1531)
  - d20 Modern
    - Streetfighting. Published by Northfield, MN: Atlas Games, 1993., D04403693T (Box BG 39, Volume 1525)
    - d20 Modern Roleplaying Game: Core Rulebook. Published by Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2002., D04563985/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2242)
    - d20 Menace Manual. Published by Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2003., D04563986+ (Box BG 39, Volume 2243)
  - Danger International
    - Urban Arcana: Campaign Setting. Published by Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2003., D04563987% (Box BG 39, Volume 2244)
  - Dangerous Journeys
    - S.H.A.D.O.W. Over Scotland (#28). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1986., D04563860W (Box BG 39, Volume 2128)
    - Epic of Aerth. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383060O (Box BG 39, Volume 1418)
    - Mythius Magick. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383062Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1416)
    - Mythus. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04382750T (Box BG 39, Volume 1111)
    - Mythus Gamemaster's Screen. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383072R (Box BG 39, Volume 1419)
    - Necropolis. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383061P (Box BG 39, Volume 1417)
  - Dark Champions
    - Creatures of the Night: Horror Enemies. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D045639970 (Box BG 39, Volume 2254)
    - Justice, Not Law (#430). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04563828- (Box BG 39, Volume 2145)
    - Shadows of the City. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04564000J (Box BG 39, Volume 2257)
    - Underworld Enemies (#431). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1993., D04563922V (Box BG 39, Volume 2171)
    - An Eye for an Eye (#432). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563921U (Box BG 39, Volume 2170)
    - Corporations (#434). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563919. (Box BG 39, Volume 2168)
    - Dystopia. Published by Roseville, MN: Atlas Games, 1994., D04563874. (Box BG 39, Volume 2159)
    - Hudson City Blues (#438). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563916Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2165)
    - Murderers' Row (#433). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1994., D04563920T (Box BG 39, Volume 2169)
    - Heroic Adventures, Volume 2. Published by Elk Grove, CA: Gold Rush Games, 1996., D04563838. (Box BG 39, Volume 2155)
  - Dark Conspiracy
    - Dark Conspiracy. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1991., D04383088Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1420)
    - Darktek. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1991., D04383086W (Box BG 39, Volume 1422)
    - Heart of Darkness. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1991., D04383085V (Box BG 39, Volume 1423)
    - New Orleans. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1991., D04383087X (Box BG 39, Volume 1421)
    - Among the Dead. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383064S (Box BG 39, Volume 1426)
    - Dark Races Vol. I Compendium. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383065T (Box BG 39, Volume 1425)
    - Hellsgate. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383066U (Box BG 39, Volume 1424)
    - Ice Daemon. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383082S (Box BG 39, Volume 1429)
    - Nightsider. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383084U (Box BG 39, Volume 1431)
    - PC Booster Kit. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1992., D04383083T (Box BG 39, Volume 1430)
    - Empathic. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1993., D04383063R (Box BG 39, Volume 1427)
    - Proto-Dimensions. Published by Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc., 1993., D04403615N (Box BG 39, Volume 1428)
  - Dark Matter
    - Dark Matter: Campaign Setting. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382647Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1029)
    - Arms and Equipment Guide. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382648Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1028)
    - The Killing Jar. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382650S (Box BG 39, Volume 1026)
    - Xenoforms: Aliens, Demons, and Aberrations. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382649- (Box BG 39, Volume 1027)
  - Dark Sun
    - Freedom. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - Arcane Shadows. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - Asticlian Gambit. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - Dragon Kings. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D03574339Y (Box BG 39, Volume 638)
    - Dune Trader. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382247U (Box BG 39, Volume 540)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix: Terrors of the Desert. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382442R (Box BG 39, Volume 814)
    - Road to Urik. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - Slave Tribes. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382248V (Box BG 39, Volume 541)
    - Valley of Dust and Fire. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382245S (Box BG 39, Volume 538)
    - Veiled Alliance. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382246T (Box BG 39, Volume 539)
    - Black Flames. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - City-State of Tyr. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382244R (Box BG 39, Volume 537)
    - Dragon's Crown. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D02340967V (Box BG 39, Volume M1)
    - Earth, Air, Fire, and Water. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382243Q (Box BG 39, Volume 536)
    - Elves of Athas. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382242P (Box BG 39, Volume 535)